{"response_code":0,"results":[{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Computers","question":"The programming language &quot;Python&quot; is based off a modified version of &quot;JavaScript&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"In &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure&quot;, Father Enrico Pucchi uses a total of 3 stands in Part 6: Stone Ocean.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"History","question":"Theodore Roosevelt Jr. was the only General involved in the initial assault on D-Day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Politics","question":"The S in Harry S. Truman stands for &quot;Samuel&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations","question":"In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"Alaska is the largest state in the United States.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"There aren&#039;t any live-action clones in &quot;Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Geography","question":"Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"For his performance at ComplexCon 2016 in Long Beach, California, Skrillex revived his &quot;Mothership&quot; set piece for one night only.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]}